Register of the Jacques Leprette papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Organizations File, 1953-2003
  - Institut Français des Relations Internationales (IFRI)
    - Printed matter
      - Newsletter, 1989 (Box-folder 153: 3)
      - Brochure, 1989 (Box-folder 153: 4)
  - Légion d'Honneur
    - Correspondence
      - 1971-1986 (Box-folder 153: 5)
      - 1987 (Box-folder 153: 6-10)
      - 1988-2003 (Box-folder 153: 11)
    - Notes, 1980 (Box-folder 153: 12)
    - Printed matter
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box-folder 153: 13)
      - Serial issues
        - 1987 (Box-folder 153: 14)
        - 1988 (Box-folder 153: 15)
    - Speeches, 1987 (Box-folder 153: 16)
  - Nouveau Cercle de l'Union, 1998 (Box-folder 153: 17)
  - Ordre National du Mérite
    - Award ceremony file
      Materials relating to Jacques Leprette's elevation to the title of Grand Officier de l'Ordre National du Mérite
      - Biographical data, undated (Box-folder 153: 18)
      - Correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 153: 19)
      - Lists of invitees, 2002 (Box-folder 154: 1-5)
      - Speeches, 2002 (Box-folder 154: 6)
    - Correspondence, 1971-2003 (Box-folder 154: 7)
    - Serial issue, 2001 (Box-folder 154: 8)
  - Société d'Histoire Générale et d'Histoire Diplomatique
    - Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 154: 9)
    - Directory, 2001 (Box-folder 154: 10)
  - Société Française pour le Droit International
    - Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 154: 11)
    - Notes, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 154: 12)
    - Papers and speeches
      - 1993 (Box-folder 154: 13)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 154: 14)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 154: 15)
    - Printed matter
      - Brochures, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 155: 1)
      - Newsletters, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 155: 2)
  - Stanley Foundation, 1974-1995
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 155: 3)
    - Notes, 1974 (Box-folder 155: 4)
    - Pamphlets, 1995 (Box-folder 155: 5)
  - United Nations Institute for Training and Research (UNITAR)
    - Bulletin, 1989 (Box-folder 155: 6)
    - Correspondence
      - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 155: 7)
      - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 155: 8)
    - Meetings file
      Correspondence, resolutions, and transcripts of proceedings
      - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 155: 9)
      - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 155: 10)
    - Notes, 1989 (Box-folder 155: 11)
    - Reports
      - 1986 (Box-folder 155: 12)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 155: 13)
      - 1990 (Box-folder 155: 14)
- Fernand Leprette File, 1916-1959
  - Biographical data, undated (Box-folder 155: 15)
  - Clippings, 1932-1939 (Box-folder 155: 16)
  - Correspondence, 1923-1941 (Box-folder 155: 17)
  - Speeches and writings
    - Les voix de l'ombre, 1916 (Box-folder 155: 18)
    - Triptyque, 1920 (Box-folder 155: 19)
    - "Georges Duhamel et la vie interieure," lecture, 1920 April 18 (Box-folder 155: 20)
    - "Georges Duhamel," Les cahiers de l'oasis, 1921 June (Box-folder 155: 21)
    - "Égypte-Europe," La Semaine égyptienne, 1928 February 9 (Box-folder 156: 1)
    - "Baigneuse," La Semaine égyptienne, 1928 April 30 (Box-folder 156: 2)
    - Salavin, ou l'homme qui veut devenir un saint, 1932 (Box-folder 156: 3)
    - "Un nouveau type littéraire, Salavin," L'ACFE, 1932 December 1 (Box-folder 156: 4)
    - Chansons de Béhéra, 1935 (Box-folder 156: 5)
    - "Le Delta du Nil," La Semaine égyptienne, 1936 April (Box-folder 156: 6)
    - "Perdu en Béhéra" and "La Sakieh," Le journal de dimanche, 1936 May 3 (Box-folder 156: 7)
    - "Visage du Nord," Revue des conférences françaises en Orient, 1937 October 1 (Box-folder 156: 8)
    - "Visite au canal de Suez," Les annales, 1939 January 25 (Box-folder 156: 9)
    - Egypt, Land of the Nile, 1940 (Box-folder 156: 10)
    - Le mauvais infirmier, 1941 (Box-folder 156: 11)
    - La huppe fantasque, 1944 (Box-folder 156: 12)
    - La rose rouge, 1952 (Box-folder 157: 1)
    - "À Berlin en 1951," Mercure de France, 1953 April/May (Box-folder 157: 2)
    - "Revenons à Melek," La revue du Caire, 1959 July/August (Box-folder 157: 3)
- Subject File, 1944-2002
  - Académie Française, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 157: 4)
  - Automobiles, Electric, 1984-2000 (Box-folder 157: 5-7)
  - Belgium--Foreign relations--France, 1986 (Box-folder 157: 8)
  - Cassin, René, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 157: 9)
  - Chareau, Pierre, 1993 (Box-folder 157: 10)
  - China--History--Nineteenth century, 1996 (Box-folder 157: 11)
  - Citations compiled by Jacques Leprette, 1950-2002 (Box-folder 158: 1-5)
  - Council of Europe, 1949-2002 (Box-folder 158: 6-7)
  - Couve de Murville, Maurice, 2000 (Box-folder 158: 8)
  - Dumbarton Oaks Treaty, 1944 (Box-folder 158: 9)
  - L'École Nationale d'Administration, 1949-1956 (Box-folder 158: 10)
  - European Union
    - 1997-1998 (Box-folder 158: 11)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 158: 12)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 159: 1)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 159: 2)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 159: 3)
  - Gaulle, Charles de
    - 1970 (Box-folder 159: 4-6)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 159: 7)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 159: 8-13)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 159: 14)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 160: 1)
  - Gary, Romain, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 160: 2)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 160: 3)
  - Hess, Rudolf, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 160: 4)
  - Human rights, 1968-1986 (Box-folder 160: 5)
  - Ma Jun, Pierre, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 160: 6)
  - Malraux, André, 1976 (Box-folder 160: 7)
  - Morocco--Foreign relations--France, 1985 (Box-folder 160: 8)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1974 (Box-folder 160: 9)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 160: 10)
  - Project Chronos, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 160: 11)
  - Proust, Marcel, 1971-1993 (Box-folder 160: 12)
  - Quebec--Politics and government
    - 1994-1995 (Box-folder 161: 1)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 161: 2)
  - Stalin, Joseph, 1953 (Box-folder 161: 3)
  - Trieste--History
    - 1945-1946 (Box-folder 161: 4)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 161: 5-10)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 162: 1-7)
    - 1947-1950 (Box-folder 162: 8)
  - Université Senghor
    - 1988 (Box-folder 162: 9-10)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 163: 1-2)
    - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 163: 3)
- Writings by Others, 1955-2001
  - Bourdon, Jêrome, 1989 (Box-folder 163: 4-5)
  - Cros, Gérard, 1982 (Box-folder 163: 6)
  - David, Marcel, 1997 (Box-folder 163: 7)
  - De Tomas Berenguer-Marco, Luis Javier
    - Undated (Box-folder 163: 8-9)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 163: 10)
  - Dupuy, René-Jean, 1983 (Box-folder 163: 11)
  - Guilhaudis, Jean-François, undated (Box-folder 164: 1)
  - Joannon, Pierre, 2000 (Box-folder 164: 2)
  - Kandji, Elhadji Mouhammadou, 1992 (Box-folder 164: 3)
  - Le Mire, Paul Herbert, 1975 (Box-folder 164: 4)
  - Luc, Robert, 1976 (Box-folder 164: 5)
  - MacVane, John, 1981 (Box-folder 164: 6)
  - Manin, Philippe, 1997 (Box-folder 164: 7)
  - Merlin, Pierre, 1990 (Box-folder 164: 8-10)
  - Modino, Polys, undated (Box-folder 164: 11)
  - Peyrefitte, Alain
    - Undated (Box-folder 164: 12)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 165: 1-9)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 166: 1-10)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 167: 1-5)
  - Piris, Jean-Claude, undated (Box-folder 167: 6)
  - Stavridi, Zinovia, 1987 (Box-folder 168: 1)
  - Sutterlin, James S., undated (Box-folder 168: 2)
  - Valère, Edmond, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 168: 3)
  - Vignes, Daniel-Henri, 1955 (Box-folder 168: 4)
- Printed Matter, 1945-2003
  - Monographs
    - 1945 (Box-folder 168: 5)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 168: 6)
    - 1948-1949 (Box-folder 168: 7)
    - 1949 (Box-folder 169: 1-2)
    - 1949 (Box-folder 170: 1-2)
    - 1953 (Box-folder 170: 3)
    - 1955 (Box-folder 170: 4)
    - 1955 (Box-folder 171: 1)
    - 1960 (Box-folder 171: 2)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 172: 1)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 172: 2)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 172: 3-4)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 173: 1-2)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 173: 3)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 174: 1)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 174: 2)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 174: 3-4)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 175: 1-2)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 175: 3)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 175: 4-5)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 175: 6-8)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 176: 1)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 176: 1-4)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 176: 5)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 177: 1-2)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 178: 1)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 178: 2-3)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 179: 1-5)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 179: 6)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 180: 1-5)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 181: 1-3)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 181: 4-5)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 182: 1-2)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 182: 3)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 183: 1-4)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 184: 1-3)
    - 1991 (Box-folder 185: 1-2)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 186: 1-3)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 187: 1-4)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 188: 1-3)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 189: 1-5)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 190: 1-4)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 191: 1-3)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 192: 1-5)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 193: 1-4)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 194: 1-3)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 195: 1-2)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 195: 3-4)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 196: 1-2)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 196: 3-5)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 196: 6-7)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 197: 1-3)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 197: 4-8)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 197: 9-10)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 197: 11)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 197: 12-15)
  - Pamphlets
    - 1961-1984 (Box-folder 198: 1)
    - 1986-1997 (Box-folder 198: 2)
    - 1998-2002 (Box-folder 198: 3)
  - Serial issues
    - 1966 (Box-folder 198: 4)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 198: 5-19)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 198: 20-40)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 199: 1-21)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 199: 22-29)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 199: 30)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 199: 31-33)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 199: 34-36)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 199: 37-40)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 200: 1)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 200: 2-8)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 200: 9-13)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 200: 14-15)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 201: 1-8)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 201: 9)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 201: 10-11)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 201: 12-15)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 202: 1)
    - 1997-1998 (Box-folder 202: 2)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 202: 3-5)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 202: 6-9)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 203: 1-7)
    - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 203: 8)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 204: 1-2)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 204: 3-4)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 204: 5-7)
- Photographs, 1941-2002
  - Jacques Leprette
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette, circa 1942 (Box-folder 205: 1)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and others, Paris, France, 1946 (Box-folder 205: 2)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette and twenty four prints depicting other individuals and various landmarks, Istanbul, Turkey, 1951 September (Box-folder 205: 3)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and his family, circa 1968 (Box-folder 205: 4)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, circa 1968 (Box-folder 205: 5)
    - One print depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette, Washington, D.C., circa 1970 (Box-folder 205: 6)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette at a wreath-laying ceremony, Washington, D.C., circa 1970 (Box-folder 205: 7)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, New York City, 1972 (Box-folder 205: 8)
    - Six prints depicting Jacques Leprette and other delegates, and one print depicting the conference building, United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, Santiago, Chile, 1972 April-May (Box-folder 205: 9)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette and other representatives, United Nations General Assembly, 1972 October (Box-folder 205: 10)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques Leprette and other representatives, United Nations General Assembly, 1973 September (Box-folder 205: 11)
    - Three prints depicting Jacques Leprette and Louis de Guiringaud, 1975 (Box-folder 205: 12)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques Leprette at the Great Wall, China, 1975 (Box-folder 205: 13)
    - Six prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others at a memorial ceremony honoring French soldiers who died in World War II, October 31 (Box-folder 205: 14)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and other representatives, United Nations Security Council, 1976 December 14 (Box-folder 205: 15)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and others at a reception, circa 1977 (Box-folder 205: 16)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others at social events, 1977 (Box-folder 205: 17)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Siteke Mwale, United Nations Security Council, 1977 January 13 (Box-folder 205: 18)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette signing an agreement establishing the International Fund for Agricultural Development, United Nations, New York, 1977 January 21 (Box-folder 205: 19)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, Andrew Young, and other diplomats, United Nations, New York, 1977 March 29 (Box-folder 205: 20)
    - Three prints depicting Jacques Leprette and other representatives, United Nations Security Council, circa 1978 (Box-folder 205: 21)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette and other member of the French delegation at an international conference, 1978 (Box-folder 205: 22)
    - Five prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others at social events, 1978 (Box-folder 205: 23)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette waiting to greet Pope Jean Paul II, United Nations, New York, 1978 (Box-folder 205: 24)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Mohammed Bedjaoui, 1978 (Box-folder 205: 25)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Robert Motherwell, 1978 May 14 (Box-folder 205: 26)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques Leprette with Valéry Giscard d'Estaing and others, New York City, 1978 May 25 (Box-folder 205: 27)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, New York City, 1978 June 2 (Box-folder 205: 28)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette with Cyrus Vance and Louis de Guiringaud, New York City, 1978 September 25 (Box-folder 205: 29)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette with Valéry Giscard d'Estaing, United Nations, New York, 1978 September 29 (Box-folder 205: 30)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Louis de Guiringaud, United Nations Security Council, 1978 September 29 (Box-folder 205: 31)
    - Six prints depicting Jacques Leprette, 1978 October (Box-folder 205: 32)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, Kurt Waldheim, and other diplomats, UN Council for Namibia meeting, United Nations, New York, 1978 October 27 (Box-folder 205: 33)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette with Kurt Waldheim and Xavier Deniau, United Nations, New York, 1979 October 25 (Box-folder 205: 34)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Jean François-Poncet, 1979 November 5 (Box-folder 205: 35)
    - Nineteen prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette and others at a party hosted by the Leprettes, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 1)
    - Thirteen prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette with their daughters, Véronique and Carole, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 2)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 3)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques Leprette with a group of schoolchildren, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 4)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and two prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 5)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette with other participants in a seminar, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 6)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette addressing a United Nations meeting, circa 1980 (Box-folder 206: 7)
    - Sixteen prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at an official dinner hosted by the Leprettes, New York City, 1980 (Box-folder 206: 8)
    - Eighteen prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others at an official reception and dinner, United Nations, New York, 1980 (Box-folder 206: 9)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette serving as president of the United Nations Security Council, 1980 January 5 (Box-folder 206: 10)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette signing the Agreement governing the Activities of States on the Moon and other Celestial Bodies, United Nations, New York, 1980 January 29 (Box-folder 206: 11)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette at a reception, 1980 February (Box-folder 206: 12)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, United Nations Security Council, 1980 November (Box-folder 206: 13)
    - Three sheets of proofs depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at a social event, 1981 (Box-folder 206: 14)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, Kurt Waldheim, Pascal Clément, and Bernard Derozier, United Nations, New York, 1981 March 2 (Box-folder 206: 15)
    - Twenty-nine prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette saying farewell to United Nations representatives from various countries, New York City, 1981 December (Box-folder 206: 16)
    - Five prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others on a tour of a research facility, 1982 October 7 (Box-folder 206: 17)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette making a speech, Ostend, Belgium, 1983 April (Box-folder 206: 18)
    - Thirty prints depicting Jacques Leprette and others at events commemorating French soldiers who fought in World War II, 1983 April 16-17 (Box-folder 206: 19)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette speaking at a seminar, Brussels, Belgium, 1983 June 1 (Box-folder 206: 20)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, 1983 June (Box-folder 206: 21)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and other participants, Eighteenth Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade, Stanley Foundation, Burgenstock, Switzerland, 1983 June 25-30 (Box-folder 206: 22)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques Leprette at a social event, 1983 July 16 (Box-folder 206: 23)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at a social event, 1983 December (Box-folder 206: 24)
    - Sixteen prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at a social event and on an excursion, 1984 (Box-folder 206: 25)
    - Twenty-six prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at an award ceremony and social event, 1984 (Box-folder 206: 26)
    - Thirty-three prints, of which one depicts Jacques Leprette, relating to an official visit to Togo, 1984 (Box-folder 206: 27)
    - Three prints depicting Jacques Leprette with other diplomats, 1985 (Box-folder 207: 1)
    - Ten prints depicting Jacques, Carina, Véronique, and Carole Leprette, 1985 (Box-folder 207: 2)
    - Seventeen prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at an official dinner, Brussels, Belgium, 1985 (Box-folder 207: 3)
    - Twenty-nine prints depicting Jacques, Carina, Christian, Véronique, and Carole Leprette at a reception and dinner, Brussels, Belgium, 1985 January (Box-folder 207: 4)
    - One print depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette, Brussels, Belgium, 1985 January (Box-folder 207: 5)
    - Four prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette, 1985 February (Box-folder 207: 6)
    - Five prints depicting Jacques, Carina, Carole, and Véronique Leprette, 1985 December 24 (Box-folder 207: 7)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and members of the Haut Conseil de Francophonie at an official dinner, Quai d'Orsay, Paris, France, 1986 (Box-folder 207: 8)
    - Six prints depicting Jacques Leprette, Montreal, Canada, 1986 February 5 (Box-folder 207: 9)
    - Eight prints depicting Jacques Leprette and Robert Bourassa, Paris, France, 1986 February 13 (Box-folder 207: 10)
    - Two prints depicting Jacques Leprette and Gil Rémillard, Paris, France, 1986 February 13 (Box-folder 207: 11)
    - Three prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at a social event, 1986 March (Box-folder 207: 12)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette and Cyrus Vance, 1986 October (Box-folder 207: 13)
    - One print depicting Jacques Leprette, 1986 November (Box-folder 207: 14)
    - Seventeen prints depicting Jacques Leprette receiving the title of Commandeur at a ceremony of the Légion d'Honneur, Paris, France, 1987 November 18 (Box-folder 207: 15)
    - Six prints depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette at a social event, circa 1990 (Box-folder 207: 16)
    - One print depicting Jacques and Carina Leprette, Basel, Switzerland, 2002 May 3 (Box-folder 207: 17)
    - Twenty-two prints depicting Jacques Leprette receiving the épée d'académicien in honor of his being made a member of the Académie des Sciences Morales et Politiques, Paris, France, 2000 June 23 (Box-folder 207: 18)
    - Seven prints depicting Jacques Leprette and his family on the occasion of his being awarded the title of Grand officier de l'Ordre National du Mérite, Paris, France, 2002 September 30 (Box-folder 207: 19)
  - Leprette family
    - Seven prints depicting Carina, Véronique, and Carole Leprette, 1982 (Box-folder 207: 20)
    - Five prints depicting Carina Leprette with a group of schoolchildren, circa 1983 (Box-folder 207: 21)
    - One print depicting Carina Leprette, 1986 July 16 (Box-folder 207: 22)
    - One print depicting Carole Leprette, 1983 (Box-folder 207: 23)
    - Seven prints depicting Christian Leprette, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1982 (Box-folder 207: 24)
    - Three prints depicting Véronique Leprette, 1983 July (Box-folder 207: 25)
    - One print depicting Fernand Leprette, undated (Box-folder 207: 26)
  - Other prints and transparencies
    - One print depicting Maxine Weygand, Algeria, 1941 (Box-folder 207: 27)
    - Four prints depicting Valéry Giscard d'Estaing, United Nations, New York, 1978 May 25 (Box-folder 207: 28)
    - One print depicting Kurt Waldheim and Louis de Guiringaud, United Nations, New York, 1978 September 26 (Box-folder 207: 29)
    - Two prints depicting Luis Javier de Tomas Berenguer-Marco, London, England, 2001 (Box-folder 207: 30)
    - Twelve transparencies depicting scenes in French Guyana, undated (Box-folder 207: 31)
    - Two prints depicting a training program, École Nationale des Cadres, Algeria, 1941 (Box-folder 207: 32)
    - Three prints depicting a villa, 1945 (Box-folder 207: 33)
    - One print depicting the first session of the United Nations Security Council, London, 1946 January 10 (Box-folder 207: 34)
    - Two prints depicting meetings of West European foreign ministers, 1950 (Box-folder 208: 1)
    - Thirty-five prints depicting French troops in Indochina, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 208: 2)
    - Three prints depicting Shirley Temple Black and other delegates at a United Nations conference, circa 1970 (Box-folder 208: 3)
    - Twenty-three prints depicting scenes in Greece, 1983 (Box-folder 208: 4)
    - Twenty-one prints depicting scenes in Alsace, France, 1984 (Box-folder 208: 5)
    - Twenty prints depicting scenes in Belgium, 1984 (Box-folder 208: 6)
    - Seventeen prints depicting scenes in Ireland, 1984 (Box-folder 208: 7)
    - Twenty-two prints depicting scenes in Tahiti, 1984 April (Box-folder 208: 8)
    - Thirty-five prints depicting scenes in Fiji, 1984 April (Box-folder 208: 9)
    - Thirty-two prints depicting scenes in French Polynesia, 1984 April (Box-folder 208: 10)
    - Twenty-five prints depicting views of a house and its surroundings in winter, Kraainem, Belgium, 1985 (Box-folder 208: 11)
- Sound Recordings, 1987, 2002
  - "L'Histoire vivante en francophonie,", 1987 (Box-folder 209: 1)
    One CD sound disc
  - "Portraits de Chine,", 2002 (Box-folder 209: 2)
- Videorecordings, 2000-2002
  - "Cérémonie de remise de son épée d'académicien à Jacques Leprette," independently produced videorecording, 2000 (Box-folder 209: 3)
    One VHS (PAL) videocassette
  - "Remise par le Chancelier de l'Institut de France Monsieur Pierre Messmer des insignes de la dignité de Grand Officier de l'Ordre National du Mérite à l'Ambassadeur de France Jacques Leprette," independently produced videorecording, 2002 (Box-folder 209: 4)
- CD Data Discs, 1946-1995, undated
  - One independently produced CD-ROM, undated (Box-folder 209: 5)
    Contains images of Jacques-Camille Paris and others
  - "Jacques-Camille Paris, premier Secrétaire Géneral, Conseil de l'Europe, 1949-1953,", 1946-1956 (Box-folder 209: 6)
    One independently produced CD-ROM containing materials relating to Jacques-Camille Paris and others